Pretty sure that's Mason.
He says, no it isn't.
The code says, we're 80% certain.
Still no disappointed.
He's behind the drums, keeping perfect time.
Then starts another pointless argument online.
Technically, actually, historically speaking.
Brother, it's a Mason.
Our jar shirt.
It's to play the true reason.
Is it perfect? Is it better? Yeah. Okay. So you're going to want to shout out in the chat if you know the answers.
They're fabulous prizes. It's excitement.
Okay, this is a panel versus game show. Okay, so what are we going to choose? We're going to choose
real or fake lore.
Two truths and a lie. It's like you say, prophecy or bogus and codex
Pluto
Or the whole deck. Okay, so I think I fixed it. So it's like there shouldn't repeat answers, but it's only a hundred
Oh, it's 250 questions right now. Okay, it's it'll be five hundred soon. Okay
Okay, so three of these are made up. One is genuine cult of Psyche Lord, which is real the complementary sigil the refundable seance
celestial recall notice
Extraterrestrial traffic enforcement, which is real it which is which is
Three are made up one is genuine, which is genuine cult lore. Okay
No, not everyone at once. I can only I can only keep track of
One and third time. I'm so sorry. Just say it's not all clamor. I mean just get I mean, it's like, you know
I mean, I'll give you know, we're proud of three is it was more fun of people to purchase
Well, um, okay, let me I'll get so let me all gets it. Let me see. I think
The complimentary sigil is real.
I clicked, oh, I clicked it, okay.
Revealed the answer.
Oh, I was wrong.
Oh, an extra-tracial traffic enforcement.
Extra-tracial traffic enforcement is real lore.
Absurdist concepts, treating alien spacecraft visitations
as subject to Earth's traffic law.
Oh, I remember that.
Issuing citations and tickets
for unauthorized airspace entry.
I think when I said that,
That's what happened. Okay. Well, but I will do a couple of complementary sigils though.
If you just ask me, I would probably do that for you. Okay. Three are made up. One is genuine,
which is real. The discontinued talisman, the certified incantation, prophetic timeshare,
or the band hammer. Which of those is real? What do you think guys? The band hammer?
That sounds good. Or do you think that there's a different one next to the
Oh, real. What do you think is real, guys? It's a band. Hello. Hello. Okay, well, I'll just say the bandhammer because I think that's the right answer. Let me see. The bandhammer.
Ah, I got it. The bandhammer is real lore. A moderation tool presented as a festive weapon, wrapped in a bow, represents the community's power to enforce boundaries and remove trolls with authority.
When is genuine cult of secular which is real the titanic metaphor the expired reincarnation the retroactive exorcism or the warranty portal
Like the wrench you like the red trucked in a bow
Okay, so what we guess why is it everyone participating?
It's a fun game. Do you know we guys do the band is over?
You didn't hear that so what do we have?
Titanic metaphor. I think that was real. Oh, I'm right
Titanic metaphor is real or saggy recurring metaphor for surviving chaotic streams
Comparing them to the sinking of the Titanic with the presence of lifeboats and rescue
representing community support and
Finding silver linings in difficult situations
Lifeboats! I need a lifeboat. Okay, we'll have it this way
What is it? Oh my gosh, these three are made up. What is genuine cul-de-sac? You know, what is real Rudolph's authority?
Interdimensional group chat the discounted talisman or the discounted ascension. What do you think guys?
You don't know. I think it's Rudolph's authority, but it's right
Rudolph's authority is real or Rudolph depicted as a disciplinary figure with authority over Christmas proceedings able to dismiss and judge behavior
Not recourse
I think that's the Christine outrun over by Rudolfslam.
Okay, three of these are made up.
What is genuine cult of psychic lore?
Which is real?
Cosmic recall notice, the boys club and the quack club,
Hexadermes decimal parental controls
are celestial group chat.
Hello?
You don't know?
Oh my God, I'm so sorry.
Okay, you don't know?
Okay, well, I think it's the boys club is the real one.
And the quack club, they know I was in those groups.
But the boys club in the quack club is real lore inside joke community concepts humorous see
Defined by satirical membership criteria being latino under 18 living in california
Or under 30 think on living in california listening to mexican music
Familiarity with streaming members are assigned quack numbers goes as quack number six
Functions as recurring comedic reference that binds the community
Three are made up when it's genuine cult of psyche lore.
What is real?
Astral warranty card, a cult homeowners association,
the vegan patriot comparison,
or astral customer support line.
I'm gonna go with the vegan patriot comparison.
What do you guys think?
The vegan patriot comparison is real lore,
a running joke where psyche repeatedly compares
his attractiveness to someone
or something called vegan patriot,
using it as a metric for validating his new appearance.
Oh, excuse me.
That's fun.
Okay.
Next, three are made up.
One is Daniel Wim.
What is real?
The recalled resurrection.
The male pain tolerance limitation.
The seasonal incantation or the notarized curse.
Anybody know?
You know?
Oh, shit.
Well, I know what it is with that male pain tolerance
because I know something I say.
Well.
Male pain tolerance is a real lore the recurring observation that men have lower pain tolerance than women and would be unable to endure
Childbirth making such an event hypothetically illegal for male bodies
Okay. Well, let me see. I'm gonna read load and see if there's any changes to the
Look new categories look at guys. This is so exciting. I mean, it's like this is so much fun
Let's go. Let's let's play the troll or not
Okay, the trollopedia is real. What are these the genuine entry? Which is the real troll or is there the troll king?
The knockoff troll draft the certified troll guild or the discount troll bloodline
Well guys, if you didn't know the troll king is real. Okay, that's a real lore
Yeah, the troll king is real a character concept based on psyche himself also made me kind of you
Okay
The Trollopedia is real. What are these? It's a genuine entry. Which is the real troll or the sock puppet troll guilds the amateur troll committee?
The sock puppet troll chapter or meowies social magic
Okay, I'm about to leave. I'm about to leave. I'm getting sick of it. Okay. Anyway, this is so
It's just one so soft. Oh my god. Meowie social magic
The witch meowie represents power. What is who's the fuck is meowie? I've never heard of the witch meowie
I need to study my own cult.
Meowie's social magic, okay?
That sounds cool.
Well, anyway, given the help on that, guys, I tried.